(Sheldon:)there's an app for that.
(Sheldon:)Let's see.
(Sheldon:)Harvey Wallbanger. Eh.
(Sheldon:)Sex on the Beach.
I hardly think so.
(Sheldon:)Rob Roy,
(Sheldon:)Silk Slipper, Mad Hatter.
(Sheldon:)Ooh!
(Sheldon:)I'll have a Rosewater Ricky.
(Penny:)A what?
You'll need pitted,
(Sheldon:)brandied cherries, gin,
rosewater,
(Sheldon:)Angostura bitters
and overproofed rum.
(Sheldon:)Now, first, dust
the cherries with sugar,
(Sheldon:)then spray them with a mixture
of rum and bitters.
(Sheldon:)Then ignite the rum,
caramel...
(Penny(pouring out a shot of tequila):)Here you go-- one
Rosewater Ricky.
(Sheldon:)That's not how it looks
in the picture.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, you know, every
bartender makes it differently.
(Penny:)Why don't you
give it a try.
(Woman at Door:)All right.
(Sheldon:)To the metric system.
(Sheldon:)I can't taste the cherries.